Yes, you look great.
はい、すごい格好してるね
Favorite food: chicken.
好きな食べ物、鶏肉
He seems quite selfish, but I think he has a strong core and is a strong person.
結構自分勝手っぽいけど、 なんか芯があって強い人だと思う
It's cool if you're 80 or above.
中80以上だとカッコイイ
Yes, please reintroduce yourself.
はい、じゃあ改めて自己紹介してください
Suba-san, I'm 19 years old.
すばさん、19歳です
Yes, you look great.
はい、すごい格好してるね
Stand up and stand there.
立って、そこに立ってください
Put your hands on the wall and stick your butt out.
壁に手をついて、お尻を突き出してください
Spread your legs and open your butthole.
足を開いて、お尻の穴を開けてください
The hair on your butt really showed off.
お尻の毛が、ガッツイ見せたな
Please show your face between your legs.
股の間に顔を出してください
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Ass, yes, yes.
お尻、そうそうそう
Anor, pussy and owner's face.
アノルとマンコと持ち主の顔
Wait, wait, this posture is good too.
ちょっと待って待って、この姿勢もいいよ
From now on, wake up.
今後、背中を起こして
Raise your back.
背中を起こして
Now, please bow your head.
じゃあ、頭を下げてください
Your butt looks really sexy.
お尻がすごいセクシーになってるね
It is said.
言われます
Will you tell me?
言われるの?
Her butt is erotic.
お尻がエロい
Is your butt erotic?
お尻がエロいです?
What?
なんて?
Her butt is erotic.
お尻がエロい
Erotic?
エロい?
Yes, keep your head down.
そう、頭を下げておいて
Why are you lowering your butt?
なんでお尻を低くしてるの?
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
My favorite food is...
好きな食べ物は...
Yakiniku.
焼肉
Yakiniku?
焼肉?
Kalbi?
カルビ?
Skirt steak.
ハラミ
Is it skirt steak?
ハラミなの?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it tan or something?
タンとかでもないの?
Skirt steak.
ハラミ
It's skirt steak.
ハラミなんだ
A simple one.
あっさりしたやつ
Isn't it easy?
あっさりしてない?
The skirt steak.
ハラミは
It's a bit oily.
ちょっと油多いから
Oh, really?
あ、 そう?
Yeah.
うん
What are your hobbies?
趣 味は何ですか?
My hobby is playing games.
趣味はゲーム
Oh, I'm playing a game.
あ、ゲームしてるんだ
What game are you playing?
何のゲームしてるの?
Mario Kart.
マリオカート
Are you playing Mario Kart?
マリオカートやってるの?
Yeah.
うん
It's something that is often done by multiple people.
結構複数人でやるやつ
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Online.
オンラインで
Is there online?
オンラインがあるの?
now.
今
I work with people all over the world.
世界中の人とやってる
Oh, seriously?
あ、マジ?
My uncle is a bit behind the times.
おじさんちょっと時代に残されてるわ
Ah, yes.
あ、 そう
What do you think about the current situation in Oklahoma?
今 のオクライナ情勢についてどう思いますか?
What do you think about the situation in Oklahoma?
オクライナ情勢についてどう思いますか?
Eh.
えー
It's not good.
良くないと
It's serious.
深刻だと
I think it's serious.
深刻だと思う
What do you think about Trump?
トランプについてどう思いますか?
He seems quite selfish, but I think he is a serious and strong person.
結構自分勝手っぽいけど、 なんか深刻で強い人だと思う
Ah, yes.
あ、 そう
Do you have any favorite idols?
なんか好きなアイドルとかいるの?
I wonder if it's different from idols.
アイドルは別にかな
Like Johnny's.
ジョニーズとか
so?
そんなに?
I don't know that.
そんなわかんない
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Yeah.
うん
is that so.
そうですか
What type of man do you like?
好きな男性のタイプはどういう人ですか?
condition.
調子
condition?
調子?
180 or more?
180以上?
If it's over 180, it's cool.
180以上だと、かっこいい
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Uncle is no good at all.
おじさん全然ダメですね
yes.
そう
Do you have a desire to get married?
結婚願望ありますか?
I'm 19.
19だもんね
Do you think you want children?
子供なんか欲しいと思う?
want?
欲しい?
What would you say to yourself in 10 years?
10年後の自分に一言ありますか?
Please save up.
貯金してください
Please save up?
貯金してください?
That's what it is.
そういうことね
That's right.
そうだな
Do you watch YouTube?
ユーチューブとか見るの?
I'll see.
見ます
What do you see?
何を見るの?
YouTube, Instagram, TikTok?
ユーチュービー、インスタ、ティクトクとか?
I guess there's a lot of YouTube.
ユーチューブ多いかな
There are a lot of YouTubers.
ユーチューブ多いんだ
Do you watch YouTubers?
ユーチューバー見てるの?
I also occasionally watch YouTubers.
ユーチューバーもたまに見るけど
Are you watching illegal videos?
違法動画見てるの?
I'm watching.
見てる
What are you watching?
何見てるの?
But I like games.
でもゲーム好きだから
Oh, the game commentary?
あ、ゲーム実況か
Game commentary.
ゲーム実況とか
That's what it is.
そういうことね
It was Tsubasa Maswaka.
マスワーカ・ツバサちゃんでした
yes.
はい
Move down, down, down.
下の方、下の方、下の方を動いてください
Yeah.
うん
Hold it in both hands.
両手に持ってください
Please spread your legs wider.
もっと足広げてください
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Is it getting better?
良くなっていますか?
Yeah.
うん
Please do it immediately.
すぐにしてください
Do you want children in the future?
将来、子ども欲しいの?
Boy, do you want kids?
少年、子供が欲しいの?
Let's start practicing making babies now.
今から子づくりの練習をしとこうね
Well then, I'll give you a lot of Kodane.
じゃあ、こだねいっぱい出すよ
Take it out.
出して
On the back side, close to Kikki.
後ろ側、キッキーと近いとな
Can it be spread out in both hands?
両手に広げられる?
see you later.
じゃあ、またね
bye bye.
バイバイ